[Vocalization] Uh's
Hi there Ren
It's been a little while,
Did you miss me?
You thought you’d buried me, didn't you?
Risky… Because I always come back
Deep down you know that…
Deep down you know I'm always in periphery
Ren aren't you pleased to see me?
it's been weeks since we spoke bro,
I know you need me
You’re the sheep, I'm the shepherd
Not your place to lead me
Not your place to be biting off
the hand that feeds me!
- Hi Ren
I’ve been taking some time to be distant
I’ve been taking some time to be still
I've been taking some time to be by myself
since my therapist told me I'm ill
And I've been making some progress lately,
and I've learnt some new coping skills
So I haven't really needed you much man
I think we need to just step back and chill
- Ren, you sound more insane than I do
You think that those doctors
are really there to guide you?
Been through this a million times
Your civilian mind is so
perfect at always being lied to
Okay, take another pill boy
Drown yourself in the sound of white noise
Follow this 10 step program, rejoice!
All your problems will be gone! Fucking dumb boy
- Nah mate, this time it's
different man trust me
I feel like things might be falling in place